Guide to the Rice University Harry Clay Hanszen College Records, 1956-2018 UA 072
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series VIII: Hanszen records, 1963-2015
  - Hanszen College Probation Reports, October 25, 2011 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Series IX: Hanszen records, 1989-2017
  - Award: Hanszen College Outstanding Intramural Sports Representative Team, 2005-06 (Box 24, Item 1)
  - El DoradO-Week playlist (CD), 2013 (Box 24, Item 2)
  - Guardian-themed clock, ca. 2016 (Box 24, Item 3)
  - Awards, 1989-1991 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Hanszen College crest pins, 2012 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Memories, 2012 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Minutes, 2015-2016 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Minutes, 2016-2017 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Photographs, 2012-2016 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Photographs: O-week, 2015 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Photobook honoring Dennis Huston, 2016 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Mr. Hanszen posters, 2015 (Map-drawer 148)
- Series X: Hanszen records, 2012-2018
  - Sub-Series A: Documents
    - Student Life Documents, 2007-2010 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Committee / Government Papers, 2008 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - O-Week Documentation, 2009-2012 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - "The Bird" Behavioral Assessment, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series B: Photographs
    - Photographs, 2005-2012 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - O-week Photographs (CDs), 2009-2012 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - O-week Photographs, 2013 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - O-week Photographs, 2015 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - O-week Photographs, 2017 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series C: Memorabilia
    - Sub-group: Cups and Mugs (Box 25)
      - Hanszen College Beer Bike plastic cup, 2012 (Box 25, Item 1)
      - "The few, the proud, the Hanszen Class of 2013" mug (Box 25, Item 2)
      - "Hanszen Class of 2018" glass (Box 25, Item 3)
      - "Hanszen College" ceramic mug, n.d. (Box 25, Item 4)
      - Shot glass with Hanszen seal, n.d. (Box 25, Item 5)
    - Light blue sunglasses with "HFH" decal (Box 25, Item 6)
    - Black sunglasses with Hanszen griffons on lens covers (Box 25, Item 7)
    - Hanszen College pen (Box 25, Item 8)
    - Hanszen logo-emblazoned peel-and-stick cardholder (Box 25, Item 9)
    - "Beeeeer Bike" sticker (Box 25, Item 10)
    - "Fresh Pints" Koozie (Box 25, Item 11)
    - "HFH" vanity license plate (Box 25, Item 12)
    - "Hanszen College" flask (Box 25, Item 13)
    - Hand towel with Hanszen Crest (Box 25, Item 14)
    - Black and White "Hanszen College" t-shirt (Box 25, Item 15)
    - Hanszen College drawstring bag (Box 25, Item 16)
    - Canvas banner signed by class of '99 (Box 25, Item 17)
    - New Hanszen building commemorative plaque, 1976-04-10